lsigraph.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy « LSIGraph

[

### LSIGraph

](https://lsigraph.com/)

Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and do not tolerate spam and will never sell, rent, lease or give away your information (name, address, email, etc.) to any third party. Nor will we send you unsolicited email.

If you choose to give your name and email address into one or more of our site’s registration forms, then we will send you emails relating to the mailing list(s) or service(s) you joined and the LSIGraph newsletter, as well as marketing offers from time to time. You may opt out of receiving future mailings from our mailing lists; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Financial information**

Financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date) is used only to charge you for the service you are purchasing. This will never be given to any third party.

**How do we protect your information?**

In order to prevent unauthorized access, LSIGraph uses strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us. We take all reasonable precautions to ensure the security of personal data stored on our system.

All your personal information is password-protected – only registered users and LSIGraph support staff have access to this information. As a registered user, you will be able to edit or delete your personal information details at any time using your own ID and password.

**Does LSIGraph share information?**

Your personal information is being provided only to LSIGraph unless we specifically state otherwise. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any person or company except where you have given us permission to do so or if the law requires it, or where in good faith LSIGraph believes such action is necessary to comply with a legal process.

**What about cookies?**

As you browse app.lsigraph.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can know your browsing history on our site. This information is used to better optimize your browsing experience by showing only the most relevant information to you.

The techniques we employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.

**Choice/opt-out**

If you would like to be removed from our database, please let us know. If you wish to stop receiving the LSIGraph newsletter or any of our mailing lists, please use the unsubscribe link in an email from each list.

**Children**

LSIGraph is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If we are made aware that information is or has been submitted by or collected from a child aged 12 or younger, we will delete this information.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the LSIGraph web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us at hello[at]lsigraph.com

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy came into effect in 2018 and was last updated on 27th June 2018. Any updates to this policy will be published on this page.
